In-game abbreviations:
Stam   => Stamina
Sens   => Sensitivity
Exci   => Excitement
Wetn   => Wetness
Tens   => Tension
MagC   => Magical Concentration
Affect => Affection
SkillL => Skill Level


 Pride
Represents slave's resistance to training.
High pride reduces effectiveness of the training.

 Lust
Represents slave's sexual desire.
High lust increases effectiveness of the training.

 Affection
Represents slave's love towards the trainer.
High affection increases effectiveness of the training.

 Taming
Represents slave's acceptance of her slavery.
As taming increase, pride decreases.

 Skill Level
Represents slave's skill in sexual acts.
Affects prostitution payment and slave's abilities to pleasure you (e.g. better handjob).
Also, the maximum value is determined by number of slave's hands.
Skill level is not taken directly, as in the actual value is [SkillLv/Max SkillLv] (in short: more hands - more training needed)

 Your Training
Represents player training skill.
High player skill means better training results and less stamina usage.

 Magical Concentration
Influences slave children mutations.
However, the child is not guaranteed to mutate even if it's at 100%.


 Blessing
Whenever a slave gets impregnated they will inherit genes from the slave that gave you blessing instead of player.
You will receive blessing whenever you end training with the slave that is [Trained]




※ Possible spoilers below
























 Stamina
The bar at the far left.
Represents slave's physical strength left
When it reaches 0% the training will end.

 Sensitivity
The thin, pink bar next to stamina bar.
Represents slave's pleasure.
When it reaches its 100%, slave orgasms.

 Excitement
The main pink bar below sensitivity bar.
Represents slave's arousal.
Effects of training are better when it's close to the sensitivity bar

 Wetness
Indicates whether slave is ready for insertion.
Slave tenstion may go up because of the pain if it's not enough

 Tension
Indicates whether slave is nervous.
High tension reduces effectiveness of the training.

 Shame
Indicates whether slave is ashamed.
High shame increases effectiveness of the training.


 Part Training
Each part has its own hiddent training parameter.


 Tools
Each tool have their own stimulation strength.
It's important to note that it sometimes can increase the slave's tension

Hand		Stimulation value：0.2		Increases affection
Mouth		Stimulation value：0.3		Increases affection
Penis		Stimulation value：0.4		Increases affection

Dildo		Stimulation value：0.35		Vibrates
Vibrator	Stimulation value：0.45		Vibrates
Drill 		Stimulation value：0.5		Vibrates
Massager	Stimulation value：0.9		Vibrates

Anal Vibe	Vibrates, used on:
 Anal		Stimulation value： 0.7
 Not Anal	Stimulation value： 0.35

Clamps		Stimulation value：0.3		Vibrates
Pink Rotor	Stimulation value：0.3		Vibrates

Anal Beads	used on:
 Anal		Stimulation value：0.4  
 Not Anal	Stimulation value：0.2  

Whip		Stimulation value：1.0   	Easier to increase taming
Feather		Stimulation value：0.25   	Easier to reduce tension
Razor		Stimulation value：0.1   	Can shave pubic hair. Easier to increase shame when doing so

Eyeband		Minor corrections to the training
Ball Gag	Minor corrections to the training


 Camera
Enables screenshots (without gui)
Also, when you finish slave's training, it's possible for her to make a "double-peace" gesture
Sometimes she'll also continue doing it for training

 [Trained] conditions:
1. Pride = 0 
2. (Lust + Affection + Taming) > 150%
3. Skill Level > 20%

 Repayment stages
1st trigger is when you have <= 3,000,000,000 debt
2nd trigger is when you have <= 1,000,000,000 debt
3nd trigger is when you have paid all the debt

 Demand
Maximum demand depends on stage of debt repayment
(Initial)8 → (1st repayment)10 → (2nd repayment)12 → (paid whole debt)15
But since there's no a hard limit it can be bigger than that

 About crossbreeding
Crossbreeds are as follows:
Child(Child(Mother.Parent1, Mother.Parent2), Child(Blessing.Parent1, Blessing.Parent2))
Unless SimpleMating is enable, in which case it is: Child(Mother, Blessing)

In short; it takes parents of mother and girl you took blessing
 (Keep in mind: if there's no blessing it simply takes player genes)