This is the dungeon.
You will have to work here as a Slave Trainer.
Let me explain your line of work...
First, visit the office to purchase new slaves for yourself.
When you do that, you'll be able train them to become sex slaves.
After proper training, you sell them to turn a profit. 
Having well behaved slaves work for you is viable as well.
Oh, and the market's demands fluctuate daily.
Should be easy to run this place, right?
Well then, do your best.
 I am expecting much from you ♥

You feel a chill...
Viola says
There's work to be done...
Explaination starts
Viola continues
Explaination continues...
Explaination continues...
Explaination ends
By the name of Slave Mother...
And so, the story begins here.