...Hmm? What's the matter?

If you don't have any money on you, you can always borrow some ♥
That said, you must pay your loan off later.
Each day I will increase your debt by 
%.
That's not much, right? Ufufu ♥
Oh right, forgot to mention, as a slave trainer you will be able to use all kinds of tools to train your slaves.

That will be all from me.
Now go work and return me some good results ♥

Viola stands
Viola asks

Viola explains
The explainations continue

She's a dangerous woman
End of conversation
The conversation ends

You answer

Lies, I can see you're broke.

Are you out of money?

! ! !
Your chains burst open.
Oh dear, now I have no choice but to raise your debt interest. Fufufu ♥

fu...
！

You bind Viola with steel chains

・・・ Ufufu ♥
It's good to be cautious, isn't it?

Viola smiles
Test them on Viola?