Did you wake up?
You fell asleep in the middle of our conversation.
You must have been really tired.
So, who are you? You do have a name, right?
Ufufu ♥ Alright then.
Let's start again.
My name is Violante.
But you can call me Viola.
Well, shall we continue?
As things are right now, you owe me a total of 
.

But don't worry...
 I have the ideal job for you.
Very profitable too, it's just perfect ♥

· · · · · ?

A blinding light
So dizzy...
An unfamiliar woman stands in front of you
There is a nice scent in the air
It's nicely warm in here

The woman speaks
The woman continues
The woman introduces herself

Awkward silence...
It's a world you don't know about

What a day
The story continues
Things carry on

That's a lot

Ufufu ♥ That's what I thought.

I don't remember any of it.

It doesn't matter if you agree or not, it's all written in here.
See? Do you understand now?