That's incredible, I never thought you'd make it ♥
Well, there's no reason for you to stay here anymore.
So do as you wish.

Oh! You don't have to answer now! Take your time...
Isn't it something that you would have to think through?

Anyway, you did good job.
Thank you, Slave Trainer.

 I can't just let you go.
 I mean, after all, earning 
 isn't that easy to do.

Thank you for your work.

You are free

Viola becomes silent
Viola panics!
The excuses continue
And so, the story ends

Basking in the afterglow...
Submerged in the afterglow...

Eh?

Go back home?