Nothing left to buy.

Dildo         
Vibrator    
Drill Vibe  
Massager    
Anal Vibe  
Whip     
Feather  
Razor     
Clamps      
Pink Rotor
Anal Beads
Eyeband  
Ball Gag 
Camera   
Floor     

Those prices are ridiculous.

A dildo that looks like a penis.
Moderate stimulation.

Common vibrator.
Stimulation is stronger than from a dildo.

A double function dildo - vibrates and rotates.

A toy with powerful vibrating ball.
Strong stimulation.

Vibrator suitable for anal training.

Training whip, a pain inducing tool.

Feather broom, Used to reduce the tension.

Standard T-shaped razor, can be used to shave pubic hair.

Attachable vibrating clamps.

Small pink rotor, provides gentle stimulation.

A tool suitable for anal training.

Tool to obscure slave's view.

A tool to block slave's mouth.

You can take pictures with it.

Expand your dungeon with additional floors to accomodate more slaves.